Engineering and Applied Sciences, College of; Records ua670
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
College of Engineering and Applied Sciences Records
2000-2015
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
State University of New York at Albany. College of Engineering and Applied Sciences.
ua670
18.66 cubic ft.
Administrative records of the College, formerly known as the College of Computing and Information, contains programs in Informatics, Computer Science, and Information Studies.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Web Archives
Administrative History
The College of Computing and Information (CCI) was originally formed in 2005 from the School of Information Science and Policy and contained the Computer Science and Information Studies departments. In 2015, the school was renamed the College of Engineering and Applied Sciences and a new program in Computer Engineering was developed.
Scope and Contents
Collection contains administrative records, such as internal assessments, meeting minutes, correspondence, budgetary information, grant proposals, and documentation of events and major programatic changes.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection has no series, the original order of the material was kept.
Acquisition Information
All items in this collection were transferred to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives by Assistant Dean Nan Carroll. 2015 August
Access
Access to this collection is restricted. Portions of the collection may contain recent administrative records and/or personally identifiable information. Please contact an archivist for more information.
Red asterisks (***) denote restricted items.
Education, Higher--United States--Administration; Web Archives; UAlbany Schools & Colleges; State University of New York at Albany.; State University of New York at Albany. College of Engineering and Applied Sciences.; State University of New York at Albany. College of Computing and Information.
- Web Archives, 2015 July 3-2016 September 28; 1; 596 captures
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Web crawling is managed through the Internet Archive's Archive-It service. This page includes links to both the university's collection and the Internet Archive's public collection.
  Surface-level crawling of www.albany.edu is performed daily which should includes most top-level webpages. Separate targeted crawls of every albany.edu subdomain are performed monthly to attempt to gather all content. This includes: www.albany.edu, www.rna.albany.edu, www.ctg.albany.edu, www.ualbanysports.com, www.albany.edu/rockefeller, www.albany.edu/cela, www.albany.edu/asrc, m.albany.edu, library.albany.edu, events.albany.edu, cstar.cestm.albany.edu, csda.albany.edu, and alumni.albany.edu
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Web Archives
  - http://www.albany.edu/ceas/ - University Archives collection, 2015 July 17-2016 September 28 (Web-archive 1)
  - WARC file for http://www.albany.edu/ceas/, (please see https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Web_ARChive for more details), 2015 July 17-2016 September 28 (Warc 1)
    Conditions Governing Access
    WARC files are very large and difficult to work with. Your request may take time to process, and we may be unable to deliver your request remotely. Please consult an archivist if you are interested in researching with web archives.
  - http://www.albany.edu/ceas/ - Internet Archive collection, 2015 July 3-2016 September 28 (Web-archive 2)
- Administrative Records, 2000-2015; 2; 15 cubic ft.
  - Academic Advisory Committee, Undated (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 1)
    Restricted, contact archivist for more details.
  - ACT (program software), Undated (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 2)
  - Advisory Board, 2008 October (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 3)
  - Advisory Board Meeting (cancelled), 2014 April (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 4)
  - Advisory Board Meeting, 2012 April 19 (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 5)
  - Advisory Board Meeting, 2009 November 17 (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 6)
  - Albany, city of, Undated (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 7)
  - ALA Accreditation 2010 (American Library Assoc.), Undated (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 8)
  - ALA Program 2010 (American Library Assoc.), Undated (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 9)
  - (ALA) American Library Association 2012, Undated (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 10)
  - ALISE (Assoc. for Library & Info. Science Statistical, Undated (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 11)
  - Alumni Association, Undated (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 12)
  - Alumni (by Geographic Area), Undated (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 13)
  - Alumni, 2004 (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 14)
  - Alumni Excellence Awards, 2012 (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 15)
  - Alumni Association Excellence Awards, 2012 April 28 (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 16)
  - Alumni Association Excellence Awards, 2013 April 20 (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 17)
  - Alumni Association Excellence Awards, 2013 (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 18)
  - Alumni Assoc. Excellence Awards, Deitsch, A., 2013-2014 (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 19)
  - Alumni Misc and Survey, Undated (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 20)
  - Alumni Giving Letters, Undated (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 21)
  - Untitled, 2012 (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 22)
  - Untitled, 2013 (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 23)
  - ASIS&T Open Source Festival, 2012 (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 24)
  - Assessments, Undated (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 25)
  - Assessments, Undated (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 26)
  - Assessments, 2011 (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 27)
  - Assessments, 2013 (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 28)
  - Assessment Plans, Undated (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 29)
  - (College) Assessment Activity, Undated (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 30)
  - Awards, Undated (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 31)
  - Program Preservation M.S.I.S. Program, 2010 (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 32)
  - 2004 Faculty Scholarly Program (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 33)
  - 2005 Faculty Scholarly Productivity Index (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 34)
  - BA in Information Science: Move from Infromation Studies to Informatics, Undated (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 35)
  - BAG-3, Undated (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 36)
  - BAG-3 Presentation, Undated (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 37)
  - Bioinformatics, Undated (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 38)
  - Bread and Roses Award - 7/18/13, 2013 July 18 (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 39)
  - Budget Hearing May 3, 2012, Undated (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 40)
  - Budget, 2010-2011 (Box 1 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 41)
  - Budget, 2009-2010 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 1)
  - Budget, 2006-2007 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 2)
  - Budget Meeting, 2006 April 3 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 3)
  - Budget, 2005-2006 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 4)
  - Budget-Grad Assistants, Undated (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 5)
  - Budget Policies, Undated (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 6)
  - Burton Lecture, 2006-2012 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 7)
  - Campus Impact Statement, Undated (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 8)
  - Capital Region Cyber Crime Partnership, Undated (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 9)
  - Cyber Security Part 1, 2000-2010 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 10)
  - Cyber Security Part 2, 2003-2008 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 11)
  - Cyber Security Research Visit, 2008 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 12)
  - Capital Region Economic Development Council, Undated (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 13)
  - Career Panels, 2008-2009 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 14)
  - Center for Technology in Government, 2002-2008 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 15)
  - Center for Legislative Development, Undated (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 16)
  - CCI 2.0 Meetings, Undated (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 17)
  - CCI 2.0 Meetings, 2012 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 18)
  - CCI 2.0 Meetings, 2013 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 19)
  - CCI 2.0 Faculty Meetings, 2008 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 20)
  - CCI Faculty Meetings, Undated (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 21)
  - CCI Advisory Working Group, Undated (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 22)
  - CCI 2.0 Summer Planning Retreat, 2013 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 23)
  - CCI 2.0 Summer Planning Retreat, 2012 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 24)
  - CCI 2.0 Summer Planning, Undated (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 25)
  - CCI 2.0 Summer Planning Retreat, 2009 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 26)
  - CCI 2.0 Summer Planning Retreat, 2007 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 27)
  - CCI PR TU Article/letter, Undated (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 28)
  - CCI Chairs, Undated (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 29)
  - CCI Chairs Meeting, Undated (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 30)
  - CCI Chairs Retreat, Undated (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 31)
  - CCI Retreat, Undated (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 32)
  - CCI Executive Committee, Undated (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 33)
  - CCI Faculty, Undated (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 34)
  - CCI Hiring Plans, Undated (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 35)
  - CCI Hiring Plans 05/06, Undated (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 36)
  - CCI History, Undated (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 37)
  - CCI MOU, Undated (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 38)
  - CCI Space Needs, 2009 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 39)
  - CCI Times (SISP), Undated (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 40)
  - CCI Welcome Back Gathering, 2009-2011; 2013 (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 41)
  - CCI WIT, Undated (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 42)
  - Community Engagement, Undated (Box 2 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 43)
  - Community Engagement, Presidents Awards, 2014 (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 1)
  - Community Engagement Red Dot Series, Undated (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 2)
  - CCUCE / Campus Comm. on Uni Community Engagement, Undated (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 3)
  - CCUCE / Dr. Andrew Furco, Undated (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 4)
  - CDLC, Undated (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 5)
  - CEG, Undated (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 6)
  - CEG/NIJ PROPOSAL, Undated (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 7)
  - CFMR Proposal, Undated (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 8)
  - CI Brochures, Undated (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 9)
  - CIFA, Undated (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 10)
  - CIFA/CSCIC Meeting, Undated (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 11)
  - CIFA Grand Opening, Undated (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 12)
  - CIFA PR, Undated (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 13)
  - CIFA Presentations, Undated (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 14)
  - CIFA Resources, Undated (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 15)
  - Clippings, Undated (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 16)
  - CNVRC, Undated (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 17)
  - Commencement Part 1, 2014 (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 18)
  - Commencement Part 2, 2014 (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 19)
  - Commencement, 2014 December (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 20)
  - Commencement, 2013 (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 21)
  - Commencement Program, 2013 (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 22)
  - Commencement, 2012 (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 23)
  - Commencement, 2011 (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 24)
  - Commencement, 2010 (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 25)
  - Commencement, 2009 (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 26)
  - Commencement, 2007-2008 (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 27)
  - Commencement, 2005-2006 (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 28)
  - CCI Valedictorian, Undated (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 29)
  - Compact Planning, Undated (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 30)
  - Compact Plan, Undated (Box 3 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 31)
  - Compact Plan CCI Raw Notes, Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 1)
  - Compact Plan CCI, Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 2)
  - Compact Plan, Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 3)
  - Compact Plan DFA Informatics, Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 4)
  - Compact Plan, Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 5)
  - Compact Plan, Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 6)
  - Compact Plan Other Units, Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 7)
  - Companies-MISC, Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 8)
  - Computer Science Cor, Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 9)
  - Computer Science, 2012 (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 10)
  - Computer Science, 2011 (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 11)
  - Computer Science, 2010 (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 12)
  - Computer Science, 2009 (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 13)
  - Computer Science Course Action Forms, Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 14)
  - Computer Science Scholarship recipient, 2014 Fall (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 15)
  - Computer Science Scholarship recipient, 2013 Fall (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 16)
  - Computer Science Scholarships, 2014-2015 (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 17)
  - Computer Science Scholarship recipient, 2015 Spring (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 18)
  - Computer Science Scholarship recipient, 2014 Spring (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 19)
  - Conference CISSE, 2003 June (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 20)
  - Conference ECPI Georgia, 2004 March (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 21)
  - Conference Penn State, Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 23)
  - Correspondence Hall, Kermit, Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 24)
  - Correspondence Herbst, Susan, Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 25)
  - Correspondence Philip, George, Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 26)
  - Correspondence Phillips, Susan, Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 27)
  - Correspondence Spencer, Melinda, Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 28)
  - Council on Competitiveness, Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 29)
  - Course Action Forms 2014 (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 30)
  - Course Action Forms, 2012-2013 (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 31)
  - Course Planning - University, Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 32)
  - CPATH, 2011 (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 33)
  - CPATH, Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 34)
  - CPATH (Executive), Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 35)
  - CPATH Proposals, Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 36)
  - CE 21, Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 37)
  - CRA Deans, Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 38)
  - Creation of College, Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 39)
  - CRISNY, Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 40)
  - CSC, Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 41)
  - NSF CPATH, Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 42)
  - Grants CPATH, Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 43)
  - Grant Proposal-NSF CPATH, 2009 (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 44)
  - Grant Proposal-NSF CPATH, Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 45)
  - Gurin, Joel Visit-CTG, Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 46)
  - PFMR, Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 47)
  - PFMR-PR, Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 48)
  - PFMR-Proposals, Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 49)
  - PFMR- Reports and Commentaries, 2009 (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 50)
  - PFMR-Resources, Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 51)
  - Course Redesign, Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 52)
  - CRA (Computing Research Association), Undated (Box 4 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 53)
  - CRA Deans, Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 1)
  - CRA Snowbird Conference, 2014 (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 2)
  - CRA Snowbird, 2010 (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 3)
  - CRA Snowbird, 2006 (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 4)
  - Lists of Names, Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 5)
  - CSCIC, Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 6)
  - CSCIC Education Sector, Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 7)
  - CSCIC Cyber Academy, Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 8)
  - Cyber Security Webcasts, Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 9)
  - CTG, Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 10)
  - Grant Proposal - Misc, Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 11)
  - Grant Proposal - NSF, 1999 (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 12)
  - Grant Proposal - RIT/NSF, Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 13)
  - CTG Brochures, Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 14)
  - CWIG, Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 15)
  - Dashboard, Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 16)
  - Deans Council History, Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 17)
  - Deans Council, 2008 (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 18)
  - Deans Office Meetings, Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 19)
  - Development Companies, Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 20)
  - Development- CA, Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 21)
  - Development- Prospects, Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 22)
  - DG.O, Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 23)
  - Digging into Data, Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 24)
  - Digigirlz, 2010; 2013 (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 25)
  - Digigirlz Event, Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 26)
  - Doctoral Review, Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 27)
  - Downtown Deans, Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 28)
  - Empire Innovative Program, Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 29)
  - Enrollment, Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 30)
  - Enrollment Planning, Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 31)
  - Equitable Contributions, Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 32)
  - Ethiopia Project, Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 33)
  - Expeditions, Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 34)
  - Faculty Activity Reports, Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 35)
  - File Mangement, Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 36)
  - FINRA, Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 37)
  - FIPSE, 2002 (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 38)
  - FIPSE, 2006 (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 39)
  - FIPSE Meetings, Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 40)
  - Financial Analysis Stream, 2004-2006 (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 41)
  - FMR Advisory, Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 42)
  - FMR, Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 43)
  - FMR-Props, Undated (Box 5 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 44)
  - Food For Thought, Undated (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 1)
  - Forensics, Undated (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 2)
  - FRAP, Undated (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 3)
  - Gates Foundation Grant, Undated (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 4)
  - Gainful Employment Reporting, Undated (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 5)
  - General Education Task Force, Undated (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 6)
  - Global Game Jam, Undated (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 7)
  - Government Relations, Undated (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 8)
  - Government Website - Commercial, Undated (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 9)
  - Grace Hopper, 2007-2011 (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 10)
  - Grade Change Forms, Undated (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 11)
  - Graduate Assistantships, Fellowships and Tuition, Undated (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 12)
  - Government Website, Undated (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 13)
  - Graduate Enrollment Target, Undated (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 14)
  - Grad Fair, Undated (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 15)
  - Grad Studies, Undated (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 16)
  - Graystone, Undated (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 17)
  - GSS Review, Undated (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 18)
  - GSS, 2011-2012 (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 19)
  - Grant Tech Connex, Undated (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 20)
  - Harriman, Undated (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 21)
  - Harriman Campus, Undated (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 22)
  - Harriman Campus Space, Undated (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 23)
  - Harriman - External, Undated (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 24)
  - Harriman Incubator, Undated (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 25)
  - Harriman - Internal UAlbany, Undated (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 26)
  - Harriman Proposals, Undated (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 27)
  - Harriman Reseach and Technology Park Part 1, 2006 (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 28)
  - Harriman Reseach and Technology Park Part 2, 2006 (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 29)
  - Health Informatics, Undated (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 30)
  - HEGIS Codes, Undated (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 31)
  - Historical Documents (Important), Undated (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 32)
  - Hitchcock, Karen (Park Strategies), Undated (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 33)
  - Holiday Cards, Undated (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 34)
  - Holiday Cards, Undated (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 35)
  - Holiday Cards, Undated (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 36)
  - Homeland Security (ARPA), Undated (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 37)
  - Homeland Security UAlbany, Undated (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 38)
  - Honors College, Undated (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 39)
  - Honors Society, Undated (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 40)
  - Husted Hall Renovations, Undated (Box 6 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 41)
  - IBM, Undated (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 1)
  - IBM, Undated (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 2)
  - IBM Collaborative Technologies, 2006-2008 (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 3)
  - IBM Pangoon, Undated (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 4)
  - IBM Proposal, Undated (Box 7 (2-Administrative Records), Folder 5)